http://www.chicagoshakes.com/home/privacy_policy

Menu
Join Email ListView Cart Login
Plays & EventsYour VisitEducationAbout UsSupport
Buy Tickets
Subscribe Peter Pan, A Musical Adventure I, ShakespeareIt Came From Outer SpaceMeasure for MeasureTwelfth NightAs You Like It
Privacy Policy
This is the web site of Chicago Shakespeare Theater.
Our address is: 800 East Grand Avenue on Navy Pier, Chicago, Illinois 60611.
We can be reached via e-mail at customerservice@chicagoshakes.com. Or you can reach us by telephone at 312.595.5656.
For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain names, but not the e-mail address (where possible).
With respect to cookies: We do not set any third-party cookies.
Chicago Shakespeare Theater will not trade or sell your email address to any other business or organization.
If you do not want to receive e-mails from us in the future please let us know by sending an e-mail to customerservice@chicagoshakes.com and provide us with the following: Name, Subscriber I.D. (if applicable) and Address.
If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new productions, discount offers or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings please let us know by e-mailing us at customerservice@chicagoshakes.com. You may also receive mailings from other reputable companies. You can, however, have your name put on our do-not-share list by e-mailing us at customerservice@chicagoshakes.com. Please provide us with your exact name and address in the e-mail and we will be sure to remove your name from the list that we share with other organizations.
Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line may receive telephone calls from us with information regarding new productions, discount offers or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such telephone calls please let us know by e-mailing us at customerservice@chicagoshakes.com.
With respect to Ad Servers: We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies.
Chicago Shakespeare Theater utilizes YouTube API Services in order to display video content on this website. By viewing video content on this site you agree to be bound by the YouTube Terms of Service and the Google Privacy Policy.
This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we Chicago Shakespeare Theater are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site, to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement policy applies solely to information collected by this web site.
From time to time we may use customer information for new unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used you should check back at our Web site periodically.
We collect information volunteered by the consumer such as survey information and/or site registrations.
Upon request we can provide site visitors with access to a description of the information that we maintain about them. Consumers can access this information by writing to us at the above address.
Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information. Consumers can have this information corrected by e-mailing us at customerservice@chicagoshakes.com.
With respect to security: When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial information we redirect visitors to a secure server. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.
If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact or e-mail us at customerservice@chicagoshakes.com.
Chicago Shakespeare Theater
Additional PagesPlays & EventsSubscribeShakes@HomeGift CertificatesYour VisitOur TheaterAudience EnrichmentAccessibilityNavy PierEducationTeaching ResourcesStudent MatineesTeacher ProgramsStudent ProgramsAbout UsAbout UsThe YardContactBoardWork with CSTHistoryPressResourcesEquity, Diversity & InclusionSupportDonate TodayWays to Give
© 2020 Chicago Shakespeare Theater on Navy Pier
800 East Grand Avenue • Chicago, IL • 60611 • Box Office 312.595.5600
